[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of the following medications reduces cholesterol?", "correct_answer": "Lipitor (atorvastatin)", "incorrect_answers": ["erythromycin", "Verelan (verapamil)", "Imitrex (sumatriptan)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jonathan Tunick is among the few people who have won an Oscar, an Emmy, a Tony, and a Grammy although he not so well known. Which best describes his work?", "correct_answer": "He is a music composer and arranger.", "incorrect_answers": ["He is a costume designer.", "He is a classical Shakespearean actor.", "He is a cinematographer."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the two main characters in the 2009 comedy The Ugly Truth?", "correct_answer": "Abby and Mike", "incorrect_answers": ["Andy and Lilly", "Rob and Michelle", "Christopher and Natalie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The word hepato, which derives from Greek, refers to the kidney.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played the Bouncer in the CATS club where Duckie was always getting kicked out in the movie Pretty in Pink?", "correct_answer": "Andrew Dice Clay", "incorrect_answers": ["Jon Cryer", "James Spader", "Andrew McCarthy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "With the passage of the Marijuana Tax Act, the United States effectively banned recreational and medicinal use of cannabis. What year was this act adopted?", "correct_answer": "1937", "incorrect_answers": ["1945", "1972", "1965"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Kiefer Sutherlands half-brother, Angus Sutherland, has a role in The Lost Boys: The Tribe.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these terms refers to a bone surgeon?", "correct_answer": "Orthopedist", "incorrect_answers": ["Osteopath", "Allopath", "Pediatrician"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "People with this disorder have difficulty engaging in everyday human interaction.", "correct_answer": "Autism", "incorrect_answers": ["Huntingtons Disease", "Cerebral Palsy", "Addisons Disease"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Charles Darwin was neglecting his studies at the University of Edinburgh, so his father sent him to Cambridge to get a Bachelor of Art degree, as the first step towards what profession?", "correct_answer": "Priest", "incorrect_answers": ["Teacher", "Medical doctor", "Artist"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the title of the first movie directed by actress Drew Barrymore in 2009?", "correct_answer": "Whip It", "incorrect_answers": ["Twist It", "Move It", "Shake It"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Approximately how much time does it take for light from the Sun to reach the Earths surface?", "correct_answer": "About 8 minutes", "incorrect_answers": ["About 37 minutes", "About 1 minute", "About 29 seconds"]}]